s asks what is the relationship between
the compound in line notation and the
adjacent Newman projection very clearly
looking at this Newman projection we've
got an O on the front and a CL on the
back so we're definitely looking at this
like this we are looking down this
carboncarbon Bond right here so that is
the carboncarbon bond that we cannot see
it is obscured by the carbon atom that
we are looking at and so what do we
notice if we are looking down that Bond
we're going to have a methyl group
projecting directly upwards so that's
right there we will have o down and to
our right because if we are in the plane
of the screen and that o is projecting
forwards from the screen it is going to
be down and to our right and then the
implied hydrogen will be down and to the
left so that's fine then looking at the
back carbon we have a chlorine atom that
is going to be up and to our right
because again